Search

* backDownloads
    
    * [### Download Alpaquita Linux
        
        A Linux OS fine-tuned for Java apps](https://bell-sw.com/pages/downloads/alpaquita/)
    * [### Download Liberica JDK
        
        Download the performant and secure runtime](https://bell-sw.com/pages/downloads/)
    * [### Download Liberica Native Image Kit
        
        A perfect tool for turning applications into native images](https://bell-sw.com/pages/downloads/native-image-kit/)
    
* backProducts
    
    cloud-native
    
    * [### Alpaquita Cloud  
        Native Platform
        
        The Cloud-native platform that provides the convenient way to create performant and secure Cloud solutions for your applications.](https://bell-sw.com/cloud-native-platform/)
    * [### Pricing
        
        We offer competitive and flexible pricing for large-scale development projects, and long-term support roadmaps.](https://bell-sw.com/alpaquita-support/#pricing)
    
    When failing to optimize cloud costs, companies can overspend up to 70%
    
    Read our report to learn more

    Linux
    
    * [### Alpaquita
        
        Full-featured operating system optimized for Java. Enjoy guaranteed support and the highest level of security](https://bell-sw.com/alpaquita-linux/)
    * [### Containers for Spring Boot
        
        Experience 100% Harmony of Alpaquita Linux and Liberica JDK Lite](https://bell-sw.com/alpaquita-containers-for-spring-boot-apps/)

    * [### Liberica JDK
        
        Java runtime for modern Java deployments](https://bell-sw.com/libericajdk/)
    * [### Liberica JDK  
        Performance Edition](https://bell-sw.com/libericajdk-performance-edition/)
    
    * [### Liberica Native Image Kit
        
        A tool to turn your applications into native images. Based on GraalVM](https://bell-sw.com/liberica-native-image-kit/)
    * [### Liberica Mission Control
        
        The convenient utility to manage and collect the data on your applications](https://bell-sw.com/liberica-mission-control/)
    * [### Liberica Administration Center
        
        The ultimate convenient Java inventory and update tool for enterprises](https://bell-sw.com/liberica-administration-center/)
    
    [Pricing
    
    Discover affordable and flexible subscription services for high-powered support
    
    ](https://bell-sw.com/support/#pricing)
    
* backResources
    
    * [### Blog
        
        The Blog about Java development, tools, management, resources, and costs](https://bell-sw.com/blog/)
    * [### Documentation
        
        All the information you need to use BellSoft’s platforms and projects](https://docs.bell-sw.com/)
    * [### Content Library
        
        Explore a diverse collection of guides, product briefs, e-books, webinars, and videos, all crafted to enhance your understanding and skills in Java programming.](https://bell-sw.com/content-library/)
    
* backSupport
    
    * [### Support for Liberica JDK
        
        Discover flexible and cost-effective support options for Liberica JDK Enterprise](https://bell-sw.com/support/)
    * [### Support for Alpaquita Linux
        
        Explore support plans for Alpaquita Linux, the only OS optimised for Java](https://bell-sw.com/alpaquita-support/)
    * [### Support for Liberica Native Image Kit
        
        Get support for the GraalVM-based tool, Liberica Native Image Kit.](https://bell-sw.com/nik-support/)
    
* backAbout us
    
    * [### Company
        
        Learn more about BellSoft, a major OpenJDK contributor](https://bell-sw.com/about/)
    * [### Newsroom
        
        Explore press releases and news about BellSoft](https://bell-sw.com/newsroom/)
    
* Contact us

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

1. General Provisions
    
    This Personal Data Processing Policy, or Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the “Policy”) defines what operational procedures BellSoft (hereinafter referred to as the “Operator”) uses to process personal data and which measures the Operator takes to protect personal data.
    
    1. The Operator shall establish as its primary goal and an essential prerequisite for doing business the complete observance of human and civil rights and freedoms in the course of personal data processing, including the protection of rights to personal and marital privacy.
    2. The Policy applies to all information that the Operator may receive about visitors to the [https://bell-sw.com](https://bell-sw.com/) website (hereinafter referred to as the “Website”).
2. General Definitions in the Policy
    
    1. Automated Personal Data Processing means the processing of personal data utilizing computer hardware;
    2. Blocking Personal Data means temporary termination of personal data processing (except for when processing is necessary to rectify personal data);
    3. Website means a set of images and content, along with computer programs and databases that ensure their availability on the Internet at [https://bell-sw.com](https://bell-sw.com/);
    4. Personal Data Information System means a set of personal data in databases, as well as information technologies and technical means ensuring their processing;
    5. Personal Data Depersonalization means actions which prevent identifying personal data belonging to a specific User or another personal data subject without further details;
    6. Personal Data Processing means any action (operation) or set of actions (operations) performed towards personal data with or without automation, including gathering, recording, systematizing, accumulating, storing, rectifying (updating, altering), retrieving, using, transmitting (disseminating, providing and accessing), depersonalizing, blocking, deleting, or destroying of personal data;
    7. Operator means a state body, municipal body, legal or physical person, organizing and (or) carrying out the processing of personal data independently or jointly with other persons, and also defining purposes of personal data processing, the structure of the personal data which are subject to processing, acts (operations) performed towards personal data;
    8. Personal Data means any information relating directly or indirectly to a specific or identifiable User on the [https://bell-sw.com](https://bell-sw.com/) Website;
    9. User means any visitor to the [https://bell-sw.com](https://bell-sw.com/) Website;
    10. Provision of Personal Data means actions aimed at disclosing personal data to a specific person or a specific range of persons;
    11. Personal Data Dissemination means any actions aimed at disclosing personal data to an indefinite range of persons (personal data transmission) or at acquainting an indefinite range of persons with personal data, including publishing personal data in mass media, posting them on information and telecommunication networks or providing access to personal data in any other way;
    12. Cross-Border Transfer of Personal Data means transferring personal data to a foreign state’s territory and delivering them to a foreign authority, a foreign physical or foreign legal person;
    13. Personal Data Destruction means any actions resulting in the irretrievable destruction of personal data with no further possibility to restore the content of personal data in the personal data information system and/or destruction of physical storage media holding personal data.
3. The Operator May Process the Following User’s Personal Data
    
    1. Full name;
    2. E-mail address;
    3. Information on previous employment and work experience, liability for military service and military registration;
    4. The Website also collects and processes depersonalized data about visitors (such as cookies) through Internet statistics services like Google Analytics and others.
    5. Further on in the Policy’s text, the data mentioned above are united by the general concept of Personal Data.
4. Purposes of Personal Data Processing
    
    1. The purpose of processing the User’s personal data is to share information with the User via e-mails.
    2. The Operator is also entitled to send the User notifications about new products and services, special offers and various events. The User can always refuse to receive such digital communications by writing a letter to the Operator at [\[email protected\]](https://bell-sw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) marked “Cancel notifications about new products, services and special offers.”
    3. Depersonalized User data collected through Internet statistics services are used to gather information about the User’s actions on the Website, improve the quality of the Website and its content.
5. Legal Grounds for Personal Data Processing
    
    1. The Operator processes the User’s personal data only provided that the User enters and/or sends them through particular forms at [https://bell-sw.com](https://bell-sw.com/). Filling out the respective forms and/or sending the personal data to the Operator, the User expresses their consent to this Policy.
    2. The Operator processes the depersonalized User data if it is allowed in the User’s browser settings (both cookies and JavaScript are enabled).
6. Procedures for Gathering, Storing, Transmitting and Other Processing of Personal Data
    
    The Operator ensures the security of the processed personal data by means of legal, organizational and technical measures necessary to fully comply with the legislative requirements for personal data protection.
    
    1. The Operator shall protect personal data and take whatever action is possible to prevent unauthorized persons from having access to personal data.
    2. The User’s personal data in no event shall be transmitted to third parties, except in cases where the law provides otherwise.
    3. Should the User uncover inaccuracies in the personal data, they may update them independently by sending an e-mail notice to the Operator at [\[email protected\]](https://bell-sw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) marked “Update personal data.”
    4. The personal data processing period is unlimited. The User may revoke their consent to the processing of personal data at any moment by sending an e-mail notice to the Operator at [\[email protected\]](https://bell-sw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) marked “Revoke consent to the processing of personal data.”
7. Cross-Border Transfer of Personal Data
    
    1. The Operator is obliged to ascertain that the foreign state to whose territory personal data is expected to be transferred provides adequate protection of personal data subjects’ right before such a transfer begins.
    2. Cross-border transfer of personal data to the territory of foreign states that do not meet the above-stated requirements may only take place with the written consent of the personal data subject to the cross-border transfer of their personal data and/or as part of an agreement, to which the personal data subject is a party.
8. Miscellaneous
    
    1. The User may receive any clarifications regarding the processing of their personal data by sending an e-mail to the Operator at [\[email protected\]](https://bell-sw.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
    2. This document will reflect any changes in the Operator’s personal data processing policy. The Policy is valid indefinitely until it is replaced with a new version.
    3. The current version of the Policy in the public domain is located on the Internet at [https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/)

Products

Resources

Company

* Contact sales
* Request support
* Contact us

Legal Documents

* Do Not Sell My Personal Information
* Privacy Preferences

ALPAQUITA, LIBERICA, BELLSOFT, the Company logos, and all related names, logos, product and service names, designs, and slogans are trademarks or registered trademarks of BellSoft or its affiliates or licensors. All trademarks, logos and brand names are the property of their respective owners.Copyright © BellSoft Corporation 2017-2024

Subscribe to our newsletter!

##### Stay up-to-date with the latest news from Java industry

First Name \*

Last Name

Business e-mail \*

Company Name

Phone

\* This field is required

I agree with [Terms](https://bell-sw.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

Contact us

Want to Know More? Contact Us!

##### Get in touch with our engineers who are always ready to help.

First Name \*

Last Name \*

E-mail \*

Phone

Company Name \*

Tell us more \*

\* This field is required

I agree with [Terms](https://bell-sw.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

Contact us

Request Liberica JDK Performance Edition for Testing!

Fill out the form below to request binaries of Liberica JDK Performance Edition for testing.

Full Name \*

Work Email \*

Company

Phone Number

Select Type

Choose JDK Version

Choose Architecture

Select Library

Select Package

Request Demo

I agree with [Terms](https://bell-sw.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/)

\* Required field.

Contact sales

##### Get in touch with our sales managers to get the best offer on support.

First Name \*

Last Name \*

E-mail \*

Phone

Company Name \*

Tell us more \*

\* This field is required

I agree with [Terms](https://bell-sw.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

Contact us

Get support

##### Get in touch with our support team and ask about our products.

First Name \*

Last Name \*

E-mail \*

Phone

Company Name \*

Tell us more \*

\* This field is required

I agree with [Terms](https://bell-sw.com/terms-of-use/) and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

Contact us

How to Fix Liberica NIK Not Starting on macOS Catalina and Later

If you use macOS Catalina and later you may encounter the issue that prevents Liberica NIK from starting. To fix it, run the following:

    sudo xattr -r -d com.apple.quarantine path/to/graalvm/folder/

If you need more help, check out the FAQ at the bottom of this page or contact us.

Thank you for choosing our runtime!

#### How will you use Liberica JDK?

To replace the current runtime

For business with specific JDK needs

For personal or educational projects

To run Java apps

Like Our Products?Help us spread the word. Review us on Gartner Peer Insights.[Leave Review](https://gtnr.io/1tGvYyLzn)

Limited Offer

Increase the Performance of JDK 8 Simply by Switching to Liberica JDK Performance edition

Work e-mail \*

Subscribe

I agree with Terms and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

\* This field is required

Limited Offer

Increase the Performance of JDK 11 Simply by Switching to Liberica JDK Performance edition

Work e-mail \*

Subscribe

I agree with Terms and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

\* This field is required

Live Webinar

**Mastering Kubernetes:**

Best Practices for Deploying Spring Boot Applications

**Dmitry Chuyko,**

Performance Architect at BellSoft

Wednesday, Aug 28, 2024

At 16:00 (GMT+8) | 10 a.m. CET

E-mail \*

Register Now

I agree with Terms and [Privacy](https://bell-sw.com/privacy-policy/) \*

\* This field is required

Warning! This domain doesn’t belong to BellSoft!

This site is not a mirror, but the copy of the official BellSoft's web page created by a third party without our permission. When you download anything from this domain, you risk installing malicious software and having your data stolen.

A Guide to Optimizing Costs of Java Cloud Deployments

##### 

Don't let cloud costs drain your resources. Take control of your Java deployments in the cloud and start maximizing your savings today.

* Companies often end up overspending by as much as 70%
* Discover the 4 key factors that drive cloud cost up
* Get the step-by-step guide to lowering your cloud costs

First Name \*

Last Name \*

Company Name

Country

Phone

E-mail \*

\* This field is required

Yes, I would like to receive communication from BellSoft. I understand I can unsubscribe at any time

Download
